So the mechanism whereby
I imagined it would
happen is that we
would make models that
were good at coding
and good at AI
research and we would
use that to produce
the next generation of
model and speed it
up to create a
loop that would increase
the speed of model
development We are now
in terms of the
models that write code
I have engineers within
Anthropa who say don't
write any code anymore
I just let the
model write the I
edit it I do
the around it I
think I don't know
we might be 6
to 12 months away
from when the is
doing most all of
what do end to
end And then it's
a of how fast
does that loop close
Not every part of
that is something that
can be sped up
by AI right There's
like There's manufacture of
There's training time for
the it's you I
think there's a lot
of It's easy to
see how this could
take a years I
don't it's very hard
for me to see
how it could take
longer than that